<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BigWing</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Red-Bold-Initial-B-Letter-Wing-Brand-Logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>BigWing</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Best linux distro 2022</title>
		<link>/best-linux-distro-2022/</link>
					<comments>/best-linux-distro-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Linux]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=315</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Linux operating system has attained such popularity that there is now a Linux distribution suited to the requirements of every computer user. We have a Linux distribution that is tailored to a high-powered, modern computing machine and an older computer with lower-end hardware. We offer a Linux distribution of only 100 megabytes and can&#8230;&#160;<a href="/best-linux-distro-2022/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">Best linux distro 2022</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-linux-distro-2022/">Best linux distro 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Linux operating system has attained such popularity that there is now a Linux distribution suited to the requirements of every computer user. We have a Linux distribution that is tailored to a high-powered, modern computing machine and an older computer with lower-end hardware. We offer a Linux distribution of only 100 megabytes and can be put on a standard disc. In addition, we offer a Linux distribution that is 4 gigabytes in size and can be installed on cutting-edge solid-state drives, which are known for their lightning-fast read/write speeds.</p>



<p>This is not the end; we also have Linux distributions exclusively for professionals, programmers, developers, and international organizations. Moreover, this is not the end.</p>



<p>So, in this article, I will provide you with a comprehensive analysis of the top Linux distributions as of the year 2021 in the following article. Don&#8217;t worry if you&#8217;re uncertain about which Linux distribution to go with if you&#8217;re considering making the transition from Windows to Linux; by the time you&#8217;ve finished reading this article, you&#8217;ll have a good idea of which Linux distribution you want to use.</p>



<h2>Ubuntu</h2>



<p><strong>Ideal for:</strong> Professionals, programmers, and regular users will find this to be a perfect Operating system.</p>



<p>The Linux distribution known as Ubuntu is one of the oldest, but it&#8217;s also widely used. Ubuntu&#8217;s rise in popularity to recognition can be attributed to the fact that it is a Linux distribution that is both user-friendly and dependable. In addition to this, Ubuntu makes it simple to transition from Windows to Linux by ensuring that widely used Windows apps can be run without difficulty on Ubuntu with the assistance of programs such as Wine.</p>



<p>Users who are new to Linux or using it for the first time might quickly feel at ease because of its intuitive user interface. Ubuntu is backed by a global network of developers committed to providing long-term support. Ubuntu has served as the foundation for developing a wide variety of Linux distributions, including LinuxMint, Kubuntu, and Lubuntu, among others.</p>



<p>Because of the Ubuntu operating system&#8217;s ever-increasing popularity and its high demand, many laptop makers have begun providing their laptops with Ubuntu already pre-installed rather than Microsoft Windows. This valuable distribution will appeal to users of all stripes, whether they are novices just starting with educational videos on the internet or seasoned professionals working as system administrators or software developers on production servers.</p>



<p><a href="https://ubuntu.com/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em><strong>Download Ubuntu from Here</strong></em></a></p>



<h2>LinuxMint</h2>



<p><strong>Ideal for:</strong> Beginners and those who have recently made the switch from Windows</p>



<p>Along with Ubuntu, LinuxMint is becoming more and more popular. It is becoming more popular with new users because it is easier to use and lighter than Ubuntu. As I already told you, LinuxMint is built on Linux. Because of this, you can feel the spirit of Ubuntu in LinuxMint.</p>



<p>It is an excellent replacement for Windows because the Cinnamon desktop gives you a desktop experience that is the same or even better than Windows. Yes, it is a perfect operating system for old computers and laptops because it doesn&#8217;t need much hardware.</p>



<p>LinuxMint, like Ubuntu, has a large online community that looks out for it. All the programs that work with Ubuntu also work well with LinuxMint.</p>



<p><a href="https://linuxmint.com/download.php" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong><em>Download LinuxMint from Here</em></strong></a></p>



<h2>Pop!_OS</h2>



<p><strong>Ideal for: </strong>Programmers and gamers</p>



<p>Pop! OS is System76&#8217;s default OS. Other PCs and laptops can download and install it for free.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s feature-rich and contemporary. Pop! OS is based on Ubuntu LTS, but it has an easy-to-use UI.</p>



<p>This Linux distro includes gaming tools, making it suitable for gamers. This distro supports hybrid graphics cards, enhancing your gaming experience.</p>



<p>Pop! OS ships with minimal apps, saving space for your favorites. Pop! The shop is like Ubuntu&#8217;s Software Center for installing programs.</p>



<p><a href="https://pop.system76.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong><em>Download Pop!_OS from Here</em></strong></a></p>



<h2>Elementary OS</h2>



<p><strong>Ideal For:</strong> Developers and creators</p>



<p>Elementary OS is another Linux distribution with a stunning graphical user interface. Its user interface is streamlined and up-to-date, much like the user interface of macOS, which it mirrors.<br>The most recent version of elementary OS is OS 6 Odin, released with a significant update to both the user interface and the set of features. Important new features include program sandboxing, multi-touch support, a dark theme, and a new installer. As a creator myself, I find that this Linux distribution, with its multitasking view, picture-in-picture mode, and do not disturb mode, is excellent for my computer.</p>



<p>Elementary OS is an open-source operating system that is free, safe, and respectful of users&#8217; privacy. Because this Linux distribution is one of the most powerful and dependable, it has the potential to become the OS of choice for computer programmers and network managers.</p>



<p><a href="https://elementary.io/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong><em>Download Elementary OS from Here</em></strong></a></p>



<h2>MX Linux</h2>



<p>XFCE, KDE, and Fluxbox are the three desktop environments included with the MX Linux distribution, a lightweight distribution of the Linux operating system. MX Linux has recently come to the forefront of the computing world and has seen a surge in popularity thanks to the strength and dependability of its operating system.</p>



<p>MX Linux is a Linux distribution that was initially made available in 2014. It is based on the Debian operating system. It comes pre-packaged with various graphical user interface (GUI) tools, which makes it very simple to use for people porting in from macOS or Windows. Because the user interface is so straightforward, even first-time users quickly feel at ease with its functionality.</p>



<p><a href="https://mxlinux.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong><em>Download MX Linux from Here</em></strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/best-linux-distro-2022/">Best linux distro 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/best-linux-distro-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Best Procreate Alternatives for Windows 10 You Should Try in 2022</title>
		<link>/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/</link>
					<comments>/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 16:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an artist or graphic designer who wants a professional app for your drawings or designs? Then Procreate is probably the best app for you nine times out of 10. But if you don&#8217;t have an iPad and can&#8217;t find any alternatives to Procreate, you&#8217;ve come to the right place. People think that having&#8230;&#160;<a href="/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">7 Best Procreate Alternatives for Windows 10 You Should Try in 2022</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/">7 Best Procreate Alternatives for Windows 10 You Should Try in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Are you an artist or graphic designer who wants a professional app for your drawings or designs? Then Procreate is probably the best app for you nine times out of 10. But if you don&#8217;t have an iPad and can&#8217;t find any alternatives to Procreate, you&#8217;ve come to the right place. People think that having an iPad is one of the best, if not the best, alternatives to having a laptop. However, many iPadOS apps, such as Procreate, don&#8217;t work on Windows machines.</p>



<h2>What is Procreate?</h2>



<p>Artists and graphic designers use the popular app Procreate to make their ideas come to life. Unfortunately, the app is only available on Apple&#8217;s iPad, but iOS users can use a less powerful Procreate Pocket version. Procreate comes with more than 130 brushes, advanced layer blending, filters, masks, etc. In addition, it has a simple and clean user interface, making it an excellent choice for any artist or graphic designer with an iPad or iPhone.</p>



<h2>Why do you need a Procreate Alternative?</h2>



<p>Windows isn&#8217;t thought of as a very tablet-friendly operating system. It has a tablet mode, and some laptops with touchscreens and a 360° hinge can be used as tablets, but most of the apps you&#8217;d want to use on a tablet aren&#8217;t made for a Windows device. So here are some of the best alternatives to Procreate for Windows that you can use to draw digitally.</p>



<h2>Autodesk Sketchbook (Free)</h2>



<p>Artists and Graphic Designers use Autodesk Sketchbook all the time. Many users think of it as the best alternative to Procreate for Windows. Autodesk Sketchbook is also free for anyone who makes an account. (Note that the Enterprise Edition costs $85 per year.) Unlike Procreate, which costs $9.99 only once, Autodesk Sketchbook can be used by anyone who makes an account. In addition, the free version has all the features without limits, which is different from other apps that charge extra for &#8220;premium features.&#8221;</p>



<p>The app also works with third-party styluses and ignores your palm when using a stylus. The app also has advanced features like an infinite canvas, 140 different brushes that you can change to your liking, a curved ruler for making perfect sweeps and curves, multiple tools, layers, and many more. The biggest problem with Autodesk Sketchbook is that it takes some time to learn how to use its controls and features. Nevertheless, Autodesk Sketchbook is a great app to use if you want something that is both free and professional.</p>



<h2>Krita (Free)</h2>



<p>Krita is a free, open-source alternative to the Windows program Procreate. It is a powerful app that lets you make everything from concept art to illustrations and comics. After the most recent update, Krita got a considerable redesign that made the app easier to use and made it look much better. In addition, Krita can work with CMYK colorspaces with 8-bit integer channels and 16-bit and 32-bit floating-point channels.</p>



<p>Krita, unlike Procreate, lets you use Vector Graphics, which enables you to make files that aren&#8217;t too big. Krita is already the best app for drawing in the Linux Community. It is also well known among Windows users. Krita also has many other features, such as using Raster Graphics and advanced layers. But, like Autodesk Sketchbook, Krita has a learning curve, and the number of components may be too much for new users. But if you take the time to learn how to use it, Krita can be one of the best Procreate alternatives for Windows.</p>



<h2>ArtRage (Paid) &#8211; $47</h2>



<p>ArtRage is one of the best Procreate alternatives for Windows that doesn&#8217;t get enough attention. It&#8217;s an excellent tool for making digital drawings with many different devices. ArtRage is a program that tries to make drawing and painting on a Windows machine much more accurate. It&#8217;s a great place to start if you want to learn about graphic design and digital illustrations. The tools are easy to use and understand so that beginners can pick them up quickly.</p>



<p>ArtRage also lets you change the way tools work to make them more useful. ArtRage has features like tracing, custom brushes, smearing, special brushes, etc. ArtRage is not a tool for professionals, so if you are a professional artist or graphic designer, we suggest you look for more professional apps on this list. ArtRage also has a few problems. It costs $47, which is a lot considering it doesn&#8217;t come with professional tools. So, ArtRage is the best Procreate alternative for Windows if you are a beginner and don&#8217;t mind spending $47.</p>



<h2>Adobe Illustrator (Paid) &#8211; $240 per year</h2>



<p>The Adobe Photo Editing and Graphic Designing Suite includes Adobe Illustrator. It is a powerful program for Graphic Designers who work in the field. Adobe Illustrator can be used to make everything from billboard ads to logos and icons. Like Krita, Adobe Illustrator supports Vector Graphics, which lets you make your final image smaller while keeping the same quality. Also, you can play with rasterization in Adobe Illustrator, just like you can in Krita and Procreate.</p>



<p>Adobe Illustrator also comes with Adobe Sense AI, which can help you work faster. Adobe Illustrator also works with other Creative Cloud apps. You can use Adobe Portfolio to make a portfolio or Adobe Fonts Plus to get fonts. Like most other Adobe apps, Adobe Illustrator costs a lot, its main drawback. So, Adobe Illustrator is for you if you are a professional Graphic Designer who already uses other Adobe Creative Cloud apps.</p>



<h2>Concepts (Free &amp; Paid) &#8211; Premium plan starts at $4.99/month</h2>



<p>The concept is an app with the same level of touch screen functionality as Procreate. It works best with the Surface Pen and Surface Pro X, but you can use it with any Stylus type. It also has support for palm rejection when a stylus is used. Concepts are also made better with ARM64 Windows machines in mind. Concepts lets you use a touchscreen Windows laptop with features like Color Dial. Like Procreate, it has almost no latency.</p>



<p>Concepts work with a lot of different brushes, pens, and pencils. It gives you ample space to draw on. Concepts also have different types of canvas that you can use to choose the texture and pattern. If you have an active stylus like a Wacom, you can use the speed feature to draw and sketch in various ways. Concepts also have Tilted and Pressured modes, which allow you to add a lot of detail to your sketches. Concepts are the closest alternative to Procreate you&#8217;ll get if you have a touchscreen device or a stylus.</p>



<h2>Corel Painter (Paid) &#8211; $450</h2>



<p>Corel Painter is one of the best Procreate Alternatives for Windows. It is a professional tool for artists and graphic designers. &#8220;Tool for the pros, made by the pros&#8221; is how it is sold. It has more than 900 different brushes, patterns, pens, fine particles, and more. Because the UI is customizable, you can take away parts of it that you don&#8217;t use. You can also put them back in if you decide you need them.</p>



<p>Corel Painter also has built-in tutorials to help people learn how to use the app. Corel Painter has a learning curve, just like some other professional apps on this list. Corel Painter costs $450, which covers all of its features. But Corel Painter is an excellent tool for you if you are a professional artist or graphic designer, or even if you are starting and want to become one.</p>



<h2>Inkscape (Free)</h2>



<p>Since Inkscape is open-source software, it is free for anyone to use. Like some of the other apps on this list, it can work with vector graphics, which lets you keep file sizes small. In addition, Inkscape has tools like an anchor, intelligent navigation, and flyout, like Procreate does. Inkscape is not the best tool for making raster graphics, but it is one of the best tools for creating vector graphics.</p>



<p>You can also use Bezier curves, spiro curves, layers, color profiles, text tools, and more with Inkscape. Inkscape also works with layers and advanced color profiles. The interface of Inkscape is clean and easy to use. So, Inkscape is the right tool for you if you don&#8217;t do a lot of raster editing.</p>



<h2>Final Thoughts</h2>



<p>Our list of the best alternatives to Procreate for Windows is over. Next, you should decide which app will serve your needs the best. For example, Are you new to this? Do you want an app that puts more emphasis on vector graphics? Do you want an app that works best on devices with touch screens? You can leave a comment below if you&#8217;re going to tell us about other great apps that we might have missed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/">7 Best Procreate Alternatives for Windows 10 You Should Try in 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/7-best-procreate-alternatives-for-windows-10-you-should-try-in-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NEXTDNS Review</title>
		<link>/nextdns-review/</link>
					<comments>/nextdns-review/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Black PirateX]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 05:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Review]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nextdns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[review]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is DNS? All website has an IP,&#160; it is necessary so that you can get all the HTML CSS, or Javascript file to render the webpage when you try to visit the website. What a DNS does is, connects your domain to your website&#8217;s server IP. We, humans, are not that good at remembering&#8230;&#160;<a href="/nextdns-review/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">NEXTDNS Review</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nextdns-review/">NEXTDNS Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="296" class="elementor elementor-296">
									<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-55746673 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="55746673" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-292bfaf1" data-id="292bfaf1" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-25ec820e elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="25ec820e" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<style>/*! elementor - v3.6.5 - 27-04-2022 */
.elementor-widget-text-editor.elementor-drop-cap-view-stacked .elementor-drop-cap{background-color:#818a91;color:#fff}.elementor-widget-text-editor.elementor-drop-cap-view-framed .elementor-drop-cap{color:#818a91;border:3px solid;background-color:transparent}.elementor-widget-text-editor:not(.elementor-drop-cap-view-default) .elementor-drop-cap{margin-top:8px}.elementor-widget-text-editor:not(.elementor-drop-cap-view-default) .elementor-drop-cap-letter{width:1em;height:1em}.elementor-widget-text-editor .elementor-drop-cap{float:left;text-align:center;line-height:1;font-size:50px}.elementor-widget-text-editor .elementor-drop-cap-letter{display:inline-block}</style>				<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2>What is DNS?</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>All website has an IP,&nbsp; it is necessary so that you can get all the HTML CSS, or Javascript file to render the webpage when you try to visit the website. What a DNS does is, connects your domain to your website&#8217;s server IP. We, humans, are not that good at remembering numbers but we can remember a name for example <strong>google.com</strong> easily. A DNS serves this purpose.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In simpler words, DNS is a phone book of the internet. It keeps track of all the domains and the IP address it&#8217;s pointing to.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2>Why you should use a custom DNS?</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Your DNS provider can see your DNS queries, which means they can see the domain you are connecting to. For example, if you have searched for what&#8217;s today&#8217;s weather on Google, they cannot see (Because google.com has SSL) what question you are typing, but they can see you&#8217;re connecting to Google. So if you are using a DNS server from Google or cloud flare, they now have all the logs of those domains you are connecting to. It is a very big privacy concern. To overcome this, we are going to use custom DNS like <a href="https://nextdns.io/?from=gy8cfv84">NextDNS</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2>NEXTDNS Features</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Nextdns is a very feature-rich DNS service. They have a free plan as well as a paid plan. Paid plans might sound expensive for something as simple as DNS, but it is worth it. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading {"level":4} -->
<h4>ADBLOCKING</h4>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>NextDNS comes with an ad-blocking built-in. It is very easy to set up. After you have created your nextdns account, you can start creating your configuration. Give it any name you want or go with the default one. Now go to the privacy section and turn on a few ad blockers. I would suggest the following adblockers.  </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><li>NEXTDNS Ads &amp; Trackers blocklist</li><li>Adguard DNS filter</li><li>Adguard tracking protection filter.</li><li>Adguard base filter.</li><li>NSA Blocklist</li><li>notracking</li></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:image {"id":304,"sizeSlug":"large"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="543" height="1024" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2-543x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-304" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2-543x1024.png 543w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2-159x300.png 159w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2-768x1449.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2-814x1536.png 814w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/05/nextdns-2.png 848w" sizes="(max-width: 543px) 100vw, 543px" /><figcaption>NEXTDNS</figcaption></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>These are some of the blocklists that I use for my NEXTDNS setup. You can always add more by clicking on Add a Blocklist option. It is pretty easy to remove too. Click on the X icon at the top right corner of each added blocklist. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading {"level":4} -->
<h4>Add your NextDNS to any device</h4>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>NextDNS offers many different ways to use your DNS across all your devices. You can use their DNS by DNS over TLS or DNS over HTTPS. They also provide IPV6 addresses too. You can use their android app to connect to nextdns through a VPN. Although better methods are available for connecting to nextdns. Check their homepage for more information.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading {"level":4} -->
<h4>Parental Controls</h4>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>NextDNS has parental control built-in. If you are a parent and you want to restrict access to certain websites you will love this feature. You can block any apps or websites within one click. You can furthermore enable safe search and restricted mode on YouTube. If your child is smart, they would try to bypass this blocking. You solve this by facilitating their block bypass methods feature.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading {"level":4} -->
<h4>Denylist &amp; Allowlist</h4>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>If this is not enough, you can always use Denylist and allow the list. Denylist lets you completely block certain websites. For example, I have blocked Facebook.com, so no matter what it won&#8217;t connect to Facebook.com and I would be &#8216;free&#8217; from Facebook tracking to some extent. Allow list is the opposite, if you have some website on allow list, it would not get blocked no matter what.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading {"level":4} -->
<h4>Analytics</h4>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Analytics and logs are there, but if you are privacy-conscious you should turn them off. But if you need to spy on someone (ahem) you can turn it on and see the domains they are connecting to.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>NextDNS is free for most people. And it&#8217;s great. You can block ads and have privacy benefits too. I&#8217;ve been using nextdns for a few years now and so far it&#8217;s been great. I&#8217;d like you to give it a try. Use our referral link to sign up here.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-7c54c50 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="7c54c50" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-bb1d75f" data-id="bb1d75f" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-6c404eb elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-id="6c404eb" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<style>/*! elementor - v3.6.5 - 27-04-2022 */
.elementor-heading-title{padding:0;margin:0;line-height:1}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title[class*=elementor-size-]>a{color:inherit;font-size:inherit;line-height:inherit}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title.elementor-size-small{font-size:15px}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title.elementor-size-medium{font-size:19px}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title.elementor-size-large{font-size:29px}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title.elementor-size-xl{font-size:39px}.elementor-widget-heading .elementor-heading-title.elementor-size-xxl{font-size:59px}</style><h3 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">Frequently asked Questions</h3>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-cbc63ea elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="cbc63ea" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-a408f98" data-id="a408f98" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-f34e253 elementor-widget elementor-widget-accordion" data-id="f34e253" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="accordion.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<style>/*! elementor - v3.6.5 - 27-04-2022 */
.elementor-accordion{text-align:left}.elementor-accordion .elementor-accordion-item{border:1px solid #d4d4d4}.elementor-accordion .elementor-accordion-item+.elementor-accordion-item{border-top:none}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title{margin:0;padding:15px 20px;font-weight:700;line-height:1;cursor:pointer;outline:none}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon{display:inline-block;width:1.5em}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon svg{width:1em;height:1em}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon.elementor-accordion-icon-right{float:right;text-align:right}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon.elementor-accordion-icon-left{float:left;text-align:left}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon .elementor-accordion-icon-closed{display:block}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon .elementor-accordion-icon-opened,.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title.elementor-active .elementor-accordion-icon-closed{display:none}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title.elementor-active .elementor-accordion-icon-opened{display:block}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-content{display:none;padding:15px 20px;border-top:1px solid #d4d4d4}@media (max-width:767px){.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title{padding:12px 15px}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-title .elementor-accordion-icon{width:1.2em}.elementor-accordion .elementor-tab-content{padding:7px 15px}}</style>		<div class="elementor-accordion" role="tablist">
							<div class="elementor-accordion-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-2551" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="1" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-2551" aria-expanded="false">
													<span class="elementor-accordion-icon elementor-accordion-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-plus"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-opened"><i class="fas fa-minus"></i></span>
														</span>
												<a class="elementor-accordion-title" href="">Is NextDNS secure?</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-2551" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="1" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-2551"><p>NextDNS prevents advertisements and trackers on websites and applications and provides a secure and supervised Internet for kids – on all devices and networks. None necessary. Set your preferences later.</p></div>
				</div>
							<div class="elementor-accordion-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-2552" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="2" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-2552" aria-expanded="false">
													<span class="elementor-accordion-icon elementor-accordion-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-plus"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-opened"><i class="fas fa-minus"></i></span>
														</span>
												<a class="elementor-accordion-title" href="">Who owns NextDNS?</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-2552" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="2" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-2552"><p>NextDNS was established in May of 2019 in the state of Delaware, United States of America, by two French entrepreneurs by the names of Romain Cointepas and Olivier Poitrey.</p></div>
				</div>
							<div class="elementor-accordion-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-2553" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="3" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-2553" aria-expanded="false">
													<span class="elementor-accordion-icon elementor-accordion-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-plus"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-accordion-icon-opened"><i class="fas fa-minus"></i></span>
														</span>
												<a class="elementor-accordion-title" href="">Is NextDNS fast?</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-2553" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="3" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-2553"><p>NextDNS is one of the best / quickest DNS providers. Both founders must be networking experts. It&#8217;s good because I have latency intolerance.</p></div>
				</div>
								</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
							</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nextdns-review/">NEXTDNS Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/nextdns-review/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Best Websites to Download Subtitles for Movies</title>
		<link>/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/</link>
					<comments>/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 03:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Subtitles are essential for modern entertainment, but finding the best places to download subtitles for movies and TV shows can be challenging. The times have changed when it comes to digital media. If someone wants to watch a movie, they have many options at their fingertips. When you watch a movie or TV show with&#8230;&#160;<a href="/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">10 Best Websites to Download Subtitles for Movies</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/">10 Best Websites to Download Subtitles for Movies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Subtitles are essential for modern entertainment, but finding the best places to download subtitles for movies and TV shows can be challenging. The times have changed when it comes to digital media. If someone wants to watch a movie, they have many options at their fingertips. When you watch a movie or TV show with subtitles, you can read meaningful dialogue even if a lot is happening or there is noise in the background.</p>



<p>Also, subtitles make it easier for people to watch videos on Netflix and Prime Video in languages other than their own. You can also download subtitles for movies in languages other than your own. This makes it more fun and can simultaneously help you learn a new language. Keeping all of these things in mind, we&#8217;ve made a list of the 10 Best Websites to Download Subtitles for Movies and Series.</p>



<h2>Downsub</h2>



<p>Downsub takes a different approach to subtitles and lets you download the subtitles for videos you watch online. The website enables people to download subtitles for online videos on YouTube, Vimeo, Daily Motion, Hotstar, Viu, and many more. This makes it different from other platforms that only offer subtitles for movies and TV shows.</p>



<p>The website has a box where you can type in the URL of the video you want subtitles for. After pasting the URL into the box, click the Download button. The subtitle will then be downloaded to your computer. After HTML tags and formatting are taken out of the file, it can be saved in two different formats: TXT and SRT.</p>



<h2>OpenSubtitles</h2>



<p>There&#8217;s no doubt that OpenSubtitles is the best place to download subtitles, as it has the largest and best database of subs for many movies and TV shows. Up to 50 different languages, such as Aragonese and Vietnamese, have subtitles on the website. The website has many subtitles to choose from and gives a detailed description of each one, including the date it was uploaded.</p>



<p>You can use the web pages from this open-source subtitles site on your websites by turning them into an XML file that can be read. You can also look at how a movie&#8217;s subtitles have been rated and what people have said about them to decide which ones to download faster. This open-source page is one of the best places to find subtitles for movies and TV shows. It has 5000 different titles all in one place.</p>



<h2>YIFY Subtitles</h2>



<p>Most people who download movies from the internet have seen the YIFY Movie site, with a long list of Hollywood movies. In the same way, the same website has pulled out its subtitles page, which has a nice-looking interface. In addition, the website has a lot of information in one place, including ratings for the movies.</p>



<p>Also, there are different types of music on the website, making it easy to choose, and a search bar is already there. Like OpenSubtitles, YIFY lets users upload subtitles in many different languages. You can download subtitles for movies from YIFY, one of the best websites.</p>



<h2>Subscene</h2>



<p>Subscene joins OpenSubtitles and YIFY as a popular website where people go to download subtitles. A filter on the website shows different subtitles for each language. Subscene is also kind enough to let people who have trouble hearing download subtitles. This is an excellent thing for the platform to do.</p>



<p>The website has a simple, older-style user interface with a few genre filters, a search box, and multiple files for a single movie or series title. Also, the Subscene has a &#8220;request subtitle&#8221; button that lets users who can&#8217;t find the file for the movie they want to download subtitles later.</p>



<p> </p>



<h2>Podnapisi</h2>



<p>Most people know Podnapisi for its English subtitles, which include up to 2 million subtitle files and more than 2 million subtitles. The website is slightly different from YIFY and OpenSubtitles in its works and looks. Changes can be seen on the homepage, which now has many features that get a lot of people to download subtitles for movies every day.</p>



<p>The website has a search engine that lets you look for files by keyword and by year, type of movie, and rating. This helps you find suitable files. Also, users can see how good a subtitle file is before downloading it by looking at the preview. The platform is the best place to download subtitles for English movies and TV shows with these features.</p>



<h2>Subtitle Seeker</h2>



<p>The Subtitle Seeker wants to show users a lot of pop-up ads. The search engine, on the other hand, is pretty good. Like the Subscene, this website and its collection bring together files from different sites and show them all in one place. There are even sub-categories on the website for movies and TV shows, making finding SRT files much more accessible.</p>



<p>The website has text files for many different file types, from 480p to Blu-Ray. Game of Thrones is one of the most popular titles on the site. The interface is pretty easy to use, except for the pop-up ads that can make it hard to find the download button. We&#8217;ve got your back in this section, too, and the controller for downloading the subtitles is at the bottom of the page.</p>



<h2>TVSubtitles.net</h2>



<p>The TV Subtitles is a simple platform with a great way to organize movies and TV shows on the home page. In addition, the website has sections like &#8220;Newest Entries,&#8221; &#8220;Most Popular TV Shows,&#8221; and &#8220;Most Downloaded Files.&#8221;</p>



<p>Also, the interface looks a lot like the other sites on this list, and it has a search box to make it easier to find a specific movie file. So you can go to the website quickly and start downloading subtitles for movies right away.</p>



<h2>Subdl</h2>



<p>If you thought TVSubtitles was too easy to use because of its simple interface, you haven&#8217;t seen the Subdl. The interface of the Subdl website is even cleaner, with categories like &#8220;popular subtitles,&#8221; &#8220;new subtitles,&#8221; and &#8220;latest movies.&#8221;</p>



<p>A language filter lets you choose from English, Dutch, Italian, French, and more. Aside from these features, the UI is very clean, and subtitle files for the same movie or TV show are kept separate in different formats.</p>



<h2>Subdivx</h2>



<p>One of the main reasons people choose the Subdivx website is that it is free and doesn&#8217;t have ads. This website has up to 560,000 subtitles, but it&#8217;s hard to use because the user interface isn&#8217;t excellent.</p>



<p>The website has a lot of files that you can download to get subtitles for movies and TV shows, but there&#8217;s a catch. The website doesn&#8217;t appear in English, and you may have trouble getting it.</p>



<h2>SRT Subtitle</h2>



<p>As the name suggests, the SRT Subtitle website only has subtitles for movies and TV shows in the SRT file format. Also, the SRT files for many films and TV shows come in up to 12 languages, which is a big deal compared to other things on the list.</p>



<p>The SRT subtitle platform has two main categories on the right side of the page, just like the other sites. There are two types of classes: TV series and movies. When you choose a category, it shows you the most recently uploaded files with their titles.</p>



<h2>How to Enable Subtitles in VLC Automatically</h2>



<p>While watching a movie or video on the media player, you can use the easy shortcuts and features of the VLC Player. But did you know that VLC can find subtitles for movies and download them simultaneously? If you don&#8217;t know about this feature, we&#8217;ll tell you how to turn on subtitles on the VLC media player.</p>



<ol><li>Open VLC Player and play the movie or TV show you want.</li><li>Click on &#8220;View&#8221; in the top menu bar to get a drop-down list of options.</li><li>Now, choose &#8220;VLsub,&#8221; which is at the end of the list.</li><li>Next, click &#8220;Search by Movie Name,&#8221; which will show you subtitle files for the same movie.</li><li>You can choose the one you want for the movie from the subtitle files that VLC has put together.</li></ol>



<h2>Conclusion</h2>



<p>Overall, the ten websites on the list are the most popular places to get subtitles for movies. However, VLsub is an even better way to get the SRT directly since it includes subtitles while the movie is playing. In recent years, the number of websites with downloadable subtitles has grown to hundreds and hundreds. Here, we&#8217;ve listed the best ones for downloading SRT files.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/">10 Best Websites to Download Subtitles for Movies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/10-best-websites-to-download-subtitles-for-movies/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Best Free Video Editing Software Programs for 2022</title>
		<link>/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/</link>
					<comments>/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 16:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=242</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wyzowl&#8217;s 2022 State of Video Marketing found in a survey that 86% of businesses still use video as a marketing tool. You&#8217;ll need good video editing software to show off your products from every angle by making professional promos for Instagram, Facebook, YouTube, and other places where brand videos are shared. Many free video editing&#8230;&#160;<a href="/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">10 Best Free Video Editing Software Programs for 2022</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/">10 Best Free Video Editing Software Programs for 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Wyzowl&#8217;s 2022 State of Video Marketing found in a survey that 86% of businesses still use video as a marketing tool. You&#8217;ll need good video editing software to show off your products from every angle by making professional promos for Instagram, Facebook, YouTube, and other places where brand videos are shared. Many free video editing programs are easy to use and help you stand out from the crowd.</p>



<p>Well-made product videos are a more exciting form of content marketing than just photos. They can make customers more likely to buy.</p>



<p>We&#8217;ve made a list of the best free video editing software for 2022 and some paid versions that aren&#8217;t too expensive. Of course, every marketer has different needs, so we&#8217;ve put together a list of some of the best parts of each tool.</p>



<h2>What is Video Editing Software?</h2>



<p>Video editing software is a collection of tools that help content creators edit, change, make, or otherwise work with a video or movie file. With video editing software that you can change, you can cut and rearrange video to make it flow better, take out parts, and add effects to make the video better. No matter how big or small, any company can use a good video editor to create compelling content.<br>Best free video editing software for desktop<br>Businesses that want to make promotional videos have a lot of desktop-based editing software to choose from. Most free mobile video editing apps don&#8217;t have as many features as free desktop video editing software. This is the most significant benefit of free desktop video editing software.</p>



<p>If you want to edit your promotional videos on a budget, check out our list of free video editor software that you can use to edit long-form content for YouTube, your eCommerce site, and several other platforms:</p>



<h2>Lightworks</h2>



<p>The best free video editing software all around</p>



<p>Lightworks has an easy-to-use interface that makes it very easy to get started. Lightworks is infact one of the more accessible and easy-to-learn Linux video editing programs on this list. It is software for editing videos with a set of detailed video tutorials.</p>



<p>Lightworks comes with a set of original stock videos and music clips that can be used in any video you edit on the program. This lets you give any marketing video a polished look.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Simple trim functions of high quality for fast and accurate video editing</li><li>Speed optimization lets you keep editing while importing new material.</li><li>Multicam editing lets you sync clips from different cameras.</li><li>Real-time sharing of team projects with complete control over who can make changes.</li><li>Videos are easy to share because they can be sent quickly to YouTube, Vimeo, Facebook, and Instagram.</li><li>A lot of different video formats can be played.</li></ul>



<p>VideoPad</p>



<p>Best free software for beginners to learn how to edit videos</p>



<p>VideoPad is a great free choice for anyone who wants to make high-quality videos without spending a dime on software to edit them. You can try out different video styles and compositions with VideoPad&#8217;s simple and easy-to-use features, such as 3D video editing and a library of sound effects.</p>



<p>You can add special effects, overlays, texts, and transitions to your videos. You can also change the colors and add sound effects. Then you can quickly and easily send all of your finished videos to YouTube, Facebook, Google Drive, and other mobile devices.</p>



<p>The only problem is that it might be too easy for people who are good at making videos. Also, it doesn&#8217;t have as many advanced features as some of the other free video editing software on this list. Still, the ability to add light effects, fine-tune colors, and overlay text and images is enough to make it worth the free download.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>One built-in screen lets you see previews of selected clips, and the other lets you see previews of the whole sequence.</li><li>Pre-made transitions that can be changed to look polished and professional</li><li>Exporting presets makes it easy to create video files optimized for specific platforms, like Facebook and YouTube, and post them straight from the software.</li><li>Tools for sharing and publishing on social media that let you share videos online right away</li><li>An massive collection of transitions and visual effects can be added to videos to make them unique.</li><li>Video optimization tools, such as stabilization</li></ul>



<h2>HitFilm Express</h2>



<p>A simple, free video editor with professional visual effects and tutorials</p>



<p>HitFilm Express may seem complicated if you don&#8217;t have much experience editing videos. It&#8217;s used to make Hollywood-style movies, after all. But it&#8217;s worth the learning curve because it&#8217;s one of the best free all-in-one video editors. HitFilm does ask you to share a status update on social media when you download the software, but that&#8217;s not a big deal.</p>



<p>HitFilm has animation tools that let you make and edit transitions between audio and video without having to make composite shots. This saves alot of time when editing videos.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>With tools like motion tracking, color pickers, and cropping, you can edit videos like a pro.</li><li>Composite shot enhancements let you move two different shots together to create strange video effects.</li><li>An automatic stabilizer that makes shaky video look steady</li><li>Make as many video and audio tracks on a timeline as possible.</li><li>An innovative trimmer that lets you change the length of your clips after you add them to the timeline</li><li>Ability to copy a set of properties from one clip and use them on another clip or the whole project.</li><li>An audio mixer lets you fine-tune sounds so that they sound professional.</li><li>There are different transitions, like push, zoom, and dissolve.</li></ul>



<h2>DaVinci Resolve</h2>



<p>The best free video editor for experts</p>



<p>DaVinci Resolve is the video editing software for many professional editors of movies, TV shows, and commercials. It combines professional 8K editing, color correction, visual effects, and audio post-production into a single production tool.</p>



<p>DaVinci lets you edit both offline and online, and its high-performance playback engine saves time when editing and trimming, even for processor-intensive file formats like H.264 and RAW. Some users may find that DaVinci Resolve has too many features. Still, the free version is excellent for more advanced projects.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Two timelines make it easy to move around, cut, and trim.</li><li>A trim interface that lets you edit down to the smallest detail.</li><li>Audio and video clips are synced up automatically by intelligent editing software.</li><li>Built-in tools for picture-in-picture effects, retiming, stabilizing, dynamic zooming, text, and audio</li><li>Face detection in your clips that creates bins automatically based on the people in each shot</li><li>High-quality motion estimation and frame rate conversions to speed up or slow down clips quickly and realistically.</li></ul>



<h2>VSDC Free Video Editor</h2>



<p>Only Windows users can use the best free video editing software.</p>



<p>The desktop video editing software from VSDC can be used for free or for a fee. Even though the free version has fewer features, it still has all VSDC&#8217;s video editing tools, like a mask tool and chroma key for green-screen effects.</p>



<p>If you can afford the full version, the tools grow to include video stabilization, strong post-production effects, slideshow/presentation features, 3D diagram templates, and direct publishing to social media.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Colour-correction tools to make your photos look more professional</li><li>A complete set of effects for making changes</li><li>Filters for photos that are easy to use, like those on Instagram</li><li>Mask tools let you hide, blur, or bring out certain elements.</li><li>Social media links for sharing videos on Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, Twitter, and Vimeo.</li><li>HEVC/H.265 (an advanced video-compression standard) keeps the highest quality at the smallest file size—essential for processing 4K and HD files.</li></ul>



<h2>OpenShot</h2>



<p>The most accessible free software for intermediate video editors to use</p>



<p>OpenShot is a great video editing program for beginners because it is easy to use. Even though more complex tools may have more editing features, OpenShot&#8217;s simple design, and easy-to-use interface make it perfect for simple editing.</p>



<p>OpenShot is a good choice for small businesses because it is easy to use and is best for resizing, scaling, trimming, snapping, and rotating clips. It also lets you scroll through credits, step-through frames, map time, edit audio, and see a preview in real-time.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Watermarks, background videos, and audio tracks can be put on as many layers as possible.</li><li>Title-card templates that can be changed</li><li>The drag-and-drop files make adding video, audio, or image files easy.</li><li>Digital video effects, such as brightness, gamma, hue, greyscale, and chroma key compositing for green-screen effects</li><li>Keyframe animation is a powerful way to make animated videos.</li></ul>



<h2>Shotcut</h2>



<p>Best open-source movie maker for audiophiles</p>



<p>Shotcut is a free, cross-platform, open-source video editor with a massive library of how-to videos. It also works with many formats, like FFmpeg, 4K, ProRes, and DNxHD. However, a word of caution: Shotcut was initially made for Linux, so some people may find it strange. Even so, it&#8217;s still a perfect editor.</p>



<p>Shotcut also has a lot of options for editing audio, which makes it perfect for people who love music. With its many tools for fine-tuning audio, users can change the bass and treble, create bandpass filters, change the gain, add dynamic compression, and do more.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>The leading multimedia framework, FFmpeg, supports the newest audio and video formats.</li><li>Native timeline editing lets users import video files directly into their project file instead of a media library.</li><li>Multi-format timeline for mixing and matching different resolutions and frame rates within a project.</li><li>Balance, bass, treble, bandpass filters, compressor, and more are among the advanced audio filters used.</li></ul>



<h2>Blender</h2>



<p>The best professional software for editing videos with a 3D creation suite</p>



<p>Blender is a free, open-source 3D creation suite that can be used to make videos. It has tools to help you create 3D models and render animations. Hundreds of developers from all over the world worked together to make the software. As a result, Blender&#8217;s software has many tools because it has a large community of users.</p>



<p>Blender is made to be a 3D animation suite. Still, it also comes with a video editor that most people should be able to use. Blender is a flexible video editor that both beginners and experts can use. It can do more complex edits like video masking and is an excellent choice for more advanced projects that may involve 3D animation.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Path-tracing engine for making animated objects look real</li><li>Advanced rendering methods to save and export your project faster</li><li>The software for making video games gives you the option to code game logic into it.</li><li>Advanced tools for animating characters with realistic movement.</li><li>an extensive collection of visual effects and short films.</li></ul>



<h2>Movie Maker 10</h2>



<p>The best free software for Windows 10 to edit videos</p>



<p>Movie Maker 10 is an easy-to-use video editing program for Windows that lets you get back to basics. It&#8217;s great for editing short video clips quickly when you need them right away.</p>



<p>Movie Maker 10 has a free version that includes all of its tools for editing videos and pictures and the ability to add captions with fonts and colors that can be changed.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Automatic preview for changes and effects</li><li>Auto-movie options that let you cut your video clips in ways that suit you</li><li>You can use the animation tab to add music, titles, and credits quickly.</li></ul>



<h2>iMovie</h2>



<p>Best free software for making videos for YouTube</p>



<p>iMovie is a popular program that comes with Mac OS. Like many other Apple apps, iMovie is easy to use and lets you move files from your drive to your workstation with a simple drag-and-drop interface. It&#8217;s a simple way to make powerful videos to help you market on YouTube.</p>



<p>IMovie saves files in Apple&#8217;s cloud is a big plus. This means you can work on your project on an iPhone, iPad, or Mac. Also, iMovie constantly gets new features and improvements because it is continuously updated.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>With 4K resolution, users can make movies that look like they belong in a theatre.</li><li>You can work on the same project on your iPad, iPhone, and Mac with cloud storage.</li><li>Dozens of professional-looking title animations were made in a studio.</li><li>Styled, modern video filters made for certain types of movies, like Westerns and sci-fi.</li><li>With built-in music, sound effects, and voiceover recording, you can always edit the sound and the picture simultaneously.</li><li>Speed controls let you speed up action scenes and slow down sports highlights.</li></ul>



<h3>Conclusion</h3>



<p>Now, so you know your options, you can try out a few to find the best free video editing software. Even though each choice has pros and cons, you should now know which free video-editing program will work best for your needs and the results you want.</p>



<p>Videos consistently get more engagement on average than pictures or text posts on all social media sites. Professionally made marketing videos can help you tell a story about your products, beat YouTube&#8217;s algorithm, grab your audience&#8217;s attention, give your brand a personality, and get the most out of your paid social ads.</p>



<p>Raise the bar on your content marketing. With so many options for free video editing software, the marketing videos for your brand can be as creative as you want them to be. Also, software for editing videos helps build your brand&#8217;s image with visuals that can be viewed on the go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/">10 Best Free Video Editing Software Programs for 2022</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/10-best-free-video-editing-software-programs-for-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Best VPN Apps For Android That You Must Try</title>
		<link>/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/</link>
					<comments>/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 04:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virtual Private Networks (VPNs) are apps that allow you to hide your IP address, access geo-restricted material, and more. VPNs are secure and stringent for users&#8217; privacy and security because of their no-logging policy and IP address masking architecture. You may easily view several Netflix libraries and other platforms with high-quality VPNs. It lets you&#8230;&#160;<a href="/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">7 Best VPN Apps For Android That You Must Try</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/">7 Best VPN Apps For Android That You Must Try</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Virtual Private Networks (VPNs) are apps that allow you to hide your IP address, access geo-restricted material, and more. VPNs are secure and stringent for users&#8217; privacy and security because of their no-logging policy and IP address masking architecture.</p>



<p>You may easily view several Netflix libraries and other platforms with high-quality VPNs. It lets you evade any geo-restrictions imposed by governments and other institutions and rigorous supplemental surveillance. The question is, which VPN program for Android is the best? If you&#8217;re curious about the solution to this question, keep reading.</p>



<h2>ExpressVPN</h2>



<p>One of our favorite VPN apps for Android is ExpressVPN. It has over 3,000 servers scattered over 94 countries and 160+ locations, giving it a significantly wider network coverage to experiment with. Unlike many other VPNs, ExpressVPN is not a member of any alliance, so your data is protected without being shared for monitoring. It has dedicated Netflix content-streaming servers and many other streaming sites and torrenting, so you&#8217;re covered.</p>



<p>ExpressVPN&#8217;s shifting IP address decreases the chances of a hacker attempting to track you. In addition, because there is minimal logging, nothing you visit or do online is saved on the servers. A kill switch, 24/7 customer assistance, and five simultaneous connections are also included.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>More than 3,000 servers in 160 locations across 94 countries</li><li>Exclusive streaming servers for Netflix, Hulu, and Prime Video</li><li>24/7 customer service and a wealth of tutorials</li><li>AES 256-bit encryption uses in the programme.</li><li>Maximum of five connections</li></ul>



<p>Price:</p>



<p>$12.95 for one month, $9.99 for six months, and $6.67 for a year (1 year)</p>



<h2>NordVPN</h2>



<p>NordVPN is a top-rated VPN app for Android smartphones on the Google Play Store. It is not a member of any monitoring alliance, which means it is safe from surveillance. The app uses Double VPN technology, which encrypts data and routes it through two different VPN servers. NordVPN presently has over 5,200 servers in 62 other locations. Within the NordVPN app, you may select server locations on a map.</p>



<p>The upgraded CyberSec malware protection, the NordLynx protocol, and split tunneling are only a few features. The service supports six simultaneous connections with dedicated IP addresses. Also included is an automated kill switch. Additionally, NordVPN has a no-logs policy, so you can be confident that no data is being logged while you&#8217;re using it.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>More than 5,200 servers in 62 places</li><li>24/7 customer support</li><li>Multiple encryption steps</li><li>Six maximum devices</li><li>30 days to return it</li></ul>



<p>Price:</p>



<p>$11.99 for one month, $4.99 for one year, and $3.29 per month (2 years)</p>



<h2>Surfshark</h2>



<p>SurfShark is one of the most potent VPN apps for Android. It has more than 3,200 servers in 65 service locations. In addition, you can use its multihop connection, which hides your IP address and what you do while on a VPN. As a result, it&#8217;s easy to connect as many devices as you want to a single SurfShark connection.</p>



<p>SurfShark is well-made, putting it at the top of the list for both new and experienced VPN users. You can also add things to it, like antivirus software. But there are some problems, like the fact that there are no dedicated streaming servers and no phone support. Also, when you choose a server, the app doesn&#8217;t show you how busy that server is, which could cause buffering if there are too many people on it.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<p>More than 3,200 servers in more than 65 server locations<br>Split tunneling and multihop connections<br>Very well-thought-out interface<br>Connecting as many devices as you want<br>Price:</p>



<p>$12.95 per month, $3.99 per month for one year, and $2.33 per month for two years, with a 30-day money-back guarantee.</p>



<h2>CyberGhost</h2>



<p>If you don&#8217;t like how free VPNs often have bugs, you should switch to CyberGhost. It&#8217;s a paid VPN service that gives you access to many features. It has more than 7,000 servers with fast connections, and all the data moving through it is encrypted with AES-256 encryption. In addition, content Blocker keeps you from seeing apps and websites that could let malware in.</p>



<p>CyberGhost&#8217;s internet speeds are breakneck. WireGuard has a rate of 1Gbps in the UK, which makes it one of the fastest VPNs. You can sign up for this VPN and enjoy it because it doesn&#8217;t keep logs, has servers in 90 countries, and has many premium features.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>AES-256 encryption Auto-kill switch for up to seven devices</li><li>Over 7,000 servers in over 90 countries</li><li>The fast Internet connection</li></ul>



<p>Prices:</p>



<p>Content Blocker costs $12.99 per month, $7.99 per month for six months, and $2.75 per month (18 months)</p>



<h2>TunnelBear</h2>



<p>TunnelBear isn&#8217;t your average person. It stores more than 10 million downloads on Google Play Store alone, which is a lot. It uses AES-256 encryption to keep all of your information safe. Its minimal logging policy gives you peace of mind that TunnelBear won&#8217;t use your information to show you ads. It has a vital server infrastructure with more than 1800 servers in 26 countries. If you like to stream content, YouTube, DAZN, and Netflix have servers just for that.</p>



<p>Even though there are some problems with the app, such as no live chat and sometimes shaky connections, you can&#8217;t choose the server&#8217;s region. TunnelBear, on the other hand, has a lot to offer as well. First, there&#8217;s VigilantBear, which has a kill switch if you ever lose your VPN connection while connecting to the internet. Its GhostBear servers use unique algorithms to route data so that it looks like it came from a service that is not a VPN.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>There are over 1,800 servers in 26 countries.</li><li>VigilantBear and GhostBear The free plan has a monthly limit.</li><li>Minimal logging policy</li><li>It is encrypted with AES-256.</li></ul>



<p>Price:</p>



<p>Five VPN connections with a monthly cap of 500 MB cost $0, TunnelBear Unlimited with five VPN connections costs $3.33/mo, and TunnelBear Teams costs $17.25/mo.</p>



<h2>Private Internet Access</h2>



<p>Private Internet Access, or PIA, is another high-quality VPN for Android devices that gives you security, privacy, and an easy-to-use VPN with more than 12,000 servers. In addition, the app has advanced VPN tools like a kill switch, WireGuard protocols, split tunneling, and tracker blocking, and that&#8217;s just the icing on the cake.</p>



<p>If you want to try out the app before paying for it, you can do so for seven days for free. There are some problems, though. For example, it&#8217;s part of the Five Eyes alliance, and the server has gone down a few times. It has reasonable prices, but you have to stay with it for more extended periods.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Standards for solid encryption</li><li>Ten connections simultaneously</li><li>Support available 24/7</li><li>Trackers, ads, and DNS malware can be blocked by splitting the tunnel.</li></ul>



<p>Price: $11.95 per month, $3.33 per month for a year, and $2.03 per month (3 years)</p>



<h2>VyprVPN</h2>



<p>VyprVPN is an Android VPN app that is just getting started. It has a network of more than 700 servers in more than 70 different countries. It has fast servers that make it easy to browse and stream content. VyprVPN is also a fun place to play games.</p>



<p>The app doesn&#8217;t keep any logs, even when torrenting, so it doesn&#8217;t store any information. Instead, the Chameleon Protocol in VyprVPN hides your activities to protect your identity and keep you anonymous on the internet. It can hook onto up to 200k IP addresses. There is no limit on how much data you can use, and VyprVPN lets you watch the match as much as you want.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Torrenting-friendly</li><li>No logs policy</li><li>700 services, over 70 server locations around the world, and over 70 countries</li><li>A kill switch for the Chameleon Protocol</li></ul>



<p>Price:</p>



<p>$15 per month or $8.33 per month for a year.</p>



<h2>Bonus</h2>



<ul><li>IP Vanish</li><li>Turbo VPN</li><li>VPNify</li><li>Proton VPN</li><li>1.1.1.1</li></ul>



<h3>Conclusion</h3>



<p>It&#8217;s essential to choose the right VPN apps for Android based on how you plan to use them. For example, it could be used to switch between Netflix servers (if it detects VPN or otherwise). It could be, among other things, to hide your actual IP address. VPNs are the best way to get around geo-restrictions and unlock features that might only be available in one country. For example, WhatsApp VoIP doesn&#8217;t work in the UAE unless you have a VPN, so you have to have one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/">7 Best VPN Apps For Android That You Must Try</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/7-best-vpn-apps-for-android-that-you-must-try/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Best lightweight screen recorder for windows</title>
		<link>/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/</link>
					<comments>/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Best lightweight screen recorder for windows If you&#8217;re looking for screen-recording tools to create presentations or tutorials, you&#8217;ve come to the right place because we think these are some of the best screen recorders available. Screen Recording is easy with software that&#8217;s worth using. It lets you share your computer activities with anyone else, makes&#8230;&#160;<a href="/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">10 Best lightweight screen recorder for windows</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/">10 Best lightweight screen recorder for windows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Best lightweight screen recorder for windows If you&#8217;re looking for screen-recording tools to create presentations or tutorials, you&#8217;ve come to the right place because we think these are some of the best screen recorders available.</p>



<p>Screen Recording is easy with software that&#8217;s worth using. It lets you share your computer activities with anyone else, makes demos and explain how to install or uninstall software, show others how to use various programs, record online video chats, make tutorial and guide to help others learn more about a specific program, capture screen for security or other purposes. And other things like creating product-related videos tutorial, lessons demo, and YouTube videos for creating e-Learning content to attract customers.</p>



<h2>What Is a Good Screen Recorder?</h2>



<p>Our list of top screen recording tools for making videos on the web includes browser-based software and other programs you download. Typically, these picks meet the following criteria:</p>



<ul><li>Easy-to-use</li><li>Records the entire or particular screen</li><li>Best for system and microphone audio</li><li>Captures various data from external sources</li></ul>



<p>One crucial fact often overlooked is that many software solutions offer high-definition (HD) recording capabilities. However, it&#8217;s also important to understand that uploading HD files takes a lot longer than uploading standard-quality videos on the web, so if you&#8217;re looking for speed and ease of use, you may want to limit your options to standard recording only when it comes down to video capture-on the fly solutions.</p>



<h2>Desktop Screen Recorder vs. Online Screen Recorder</h2>



<p>Web and desktop screen recorders have distinct differences in usage methods.</p>



<p>While desktop screen recording options don&#8217;t require an active internet connection, as long as you can save the videos/audio locally to avoid losing them, online screen recorders do. They need a stable internet connection to upload the video to their servers.</p>



<p>An online screen recorder isn&#8217;t the best option if you&#8217;re looking to capture gameplay. However, they work great if you want to showcase your tutorial.</p>



<h2>Top 10 Screen Recorder Tools</h2>



<h3>1) Loom</h3>



<p>When it comes to video call solutions, Loom is the leader in the market. Their app allows you to record, share, and interact with videos at high speed. With over 14 million active users across 200,000 companies worldwide, there&#8217;s never been a better time to take your communication skills to the next level with Loom and become one of the thousands of people using this innovative solution in all walks of life right now!</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Using the original Windows software or a Chrome extension, you can record your screen in seconds.</li><li>It generates a written transcript.</li><li>Unlimited video creation and also includes a Business Plan.</li><li>Upload videos into Loom to store content in the library.</li><li>Includes emoji reaction.</li><li>Record with background noise reduction feature.</li></ul>



<h3>2) Screencast-O-Matic</h3>



<p>Screencast-O-Matic is a friendly application to use. It includes the ability to add video from your webcam and narration from your microphone for an even more pleasurable experience. It&#8217;s simple, straightforward, and does what it needs to.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>It allows you to animate films with various effects and import videos, photos, and audio from other devices.</li><li>The cursor and webcam can be shown or hidden.</li><li>To emphasize a specific movie area, zoom in or out.</li><li>Narration, music, and system audio can be added and edited. Text, shapes, and images can all be styled.</li></ul>



<h3>3) Scribe</h3>



<p>Scribe is an app that helps you create step-by-step instructions by capturing your onscreen activity, allowing you to capture the steps via text and images. Your annotated content can be embedded in any help center or knowledge base, and the Scribe browser extension is free with unlimited use.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Instantly create step-by-step instructions</li><li>Unlimited guides</li><li>Unlimited pages</li><li>Embeddable directions within any other web app</li><li>Customisable steps and instructions.</li></ul>



<h3>4) ActivePresenter</h3>



<p>ActivePresenter is visual recording software that allows users to record webcam, audio system, and narration into a single video file. ActivePresenter is a software demonstration tool that may be downloaded and used on Windows, Linux, and Mac operating systems.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>The screen can be quickly recorded as a full-motion video.&nbsp;</li><li>It enables you to record audio from the microphone and speaker.</li><li>You can integrate live-action footage into your video.</li><li>It enables you to export content to</li><li>You can export content in various video formats like AVI, MP4, MKV, WMV, and WebM.</li><li>This software support HTML5.</li></ul>



<h3>5) Movavi Screen Recorder</h3>



<p>Movavi Screen Recorder is one of today&#8217;s most popular and widely used free tools in the market to record videos. It helps you capture videos at 60 frames per second (FPS) with a sound, which is also in full HD quality.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>Use a plugin, microphone, or sound to record the screen or record a voice.&nbsp;</li><li>Include a variety of options, such as frame rate and volume.&nbsp;</li><li>Without any difficulty, you can edit and merge video segments.</li><li>This program allows you to record videos even when not present.</li><li>You can upload your work to Google Drive, Movavi Cloud, or YouTube. *&nbsp; Capturing screen audio does not require any specific hardware.&nbsp;<br>*Any source, including mic, system sounds, and camera, can be recorded.</li></ul>



<h3>6) Icecream Screen Recorder</h3>



<p>Icecream Screen Recorder is a screen capture utility that lets you record a portion of your computer screen. You may also use this video recorder to capture gameplays, live streaming, webinars, etc.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>You can set the output quality and record a specific screen region or the entire screen.&nbsp;</li><li>You can use this software to record screens using a webcam overlay.</li><li>Text, shapes, and arrows can be added to your screen recording.</li><li>You may record full-screen 3D games with Icecream applications.</li><li>It allows you to add a logo to your screen recording as a watermark.</li></ul>



<h3>7) ClickUp</h3>



<p>We all need to communicate with our team members to be better productive. ClickUp is a free screen recording solution that eliminates the need for emails or meetings by allowing users to create presentations, record their computer&#8217;s screens, add and edit text-based notes directly on their presentations, and quickly import and export content.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>It helps you capture your entire screen, app window, or browser tab.</li><li>It allows you to send your video message to anyone with a shareable link.</li><li>You can create a video recording, add a description, and assign it to your team.</li><li>Supported platforms are Windows, Mac, Android, and iOS.</li></ul>



<h3>8) Camtasia</h3>



<p>Camtasia helps people quickly create professional-looking videos on Windows and Mac. Using Camtasia, you can record your screen action and narration, and music included in your video. In addition, Camtasia will capture everything you&#8217;ll need so that it won&#8217;t take time for you to edit the content later on.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>It has a webcam, screen, presentation recording feature, and a piece of music and audio library.</li><li>You can make titles and notes that stand out.&nbsp;</li><li>You can use it to add Zoom, Pan, and Animation.</li><li>To increase video flow, employ transitions between scenes and slides. *&nbsp;You can make quizzes with Camtasia.&nbsp;</li><li>You may give your video a special effect.</li></ul>



<h3>9) PassFab Screen Recorder</h3>



<p>PassFab Screen Recorder is a freeware that allows you to record any activities performed on the computer screen freely. For example, you can capture videos of presentations, meetings, lectures, and training courses for later viewing or sharing with others who couldn&#8217;t attend.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>You can record your screen, webcam + screen, game window + your face, or just your face without recording the screen.&nbsp;</li><li>It can record mouse movements on the screen.&nbsp;</li><li>It allows you to record keystrokes on the screen.&nbsp;</li><li>It allows you to record screens with no time limit and choose between Schedule recording and segment recording.&nbsp;</li><li>It has frame rates of 15, 30, 45, and 60.&nbsp;</li><li>It supports the following resolutions: 640<em>480, 1280</em>720, 1920<em>1080, 2560</em>1440, and original.&nbsp;</li><li>The output formats are MP4 and MKV.&nbsp;</li><li>PassFab Screen Recorder will soon have editing capabilities.</li></ul>



<h3>10) AnyMP4 Screen Recorder</h3>



<p>AnyMP4 is one of the top free screen recorder software for recording all your computer activities/screenplays. The Best Screen Recorder not only can help you record any webpage or flash video from the internet but also add various sound sources from system audio, microphone voice, and take screenshots.</p>



<p>Features:</p>



<ul><li>It enables you to capture Live Streaming Videos from YouTube, Facebook, Twitch, and other social media networks.</li><li>You can capture gaming on your screen and share it with others.</li><li>Webcam Video, Audio Calls &amp; Conferences, and Microphone Voice can all be recorded.</li></ul>



<h2>Factors before choosing the best Screen Recorder</h2>



<ul><li>Ease of Use</li><li>Editing Functionalities</li><li>Screen Capturing Options</li><li>Is it Free or Paid</li><li>Screen recording software Hardware/Software Requirements</li><li>Support and Update Policy</li><li>Company reviews for the software supplier Screen Recorder</li></ul>



<h3>Conclusion:</h3>



<p>Screen recording software may serve many purposes, but you don&#8217;t have to break the bank to use it. While the most powerful and professional software programs can cost hundreds or thousands of dollars, some cheaper options are on the market for those looking for simple ways to record and share their screens. But if you are looking for professional and best tools, you should always sign up for the paid option.</p>



<p>Hopefully, one of these screen recording programs will fulfill your needs and finally make it possible for you to either create a tutorial for YouTube or focus on sharing gaming victories with your friends.</p>



<p>Do you use any other screen recorder apart from above mentioned? Let us know in the comment section below!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/">10 Best lightweight screen recorder for windows</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/10-best-lightweight-screen-recorder-for-windows/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is SEO and why is it important?</title>
		<link>/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/</link>
					<comments>/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sandeepgupta_]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=64</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Search Engine Optimization (SEO) is a vital activity any website owner should do daily. This post describes what Search Engine Optimization is, how it helps you increase traffic to your website and tactics for optimizing your website according to industry and ranking. What is Search Engine Optimization? Search engine optimization (SEO) improves the visibility and&#8230;&#160;<a href="/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/" class="" rel="bookmark">Read More &#187;<span class="screen-reader-text">What is SEO and why is it important?</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/">What is SEO and why is it important?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Search Engine Optimization (SEO) is a vital activity any website owner should do daily. This post describes what Search Engine Optimization is, how it helps you increase traffic to your website and tactics for optimizing your website according to industry and ranking.</p>



<h2>What is Search Engine Optimization?</h2>



<p>Search engine optimization (SEO) improves the visibility and ranking of the web page in search engine results pages (SERPs). By optimizing a site for search engines, one can increase traffic and encourage users to find, explore, and buy products or services from the site. SEO has become an increasingly important factor in website success in recent years. According to Quora, &#8220;93% of online shoppers start their search for a product or service on a search engine.&#8221;</p>



<p>There are many different ways to optimize your site for SEO. The most effective methods vary depending on your website&#8217;s content and online presence. Here are some common SEO strategies:</p>



<ol><li>Create optimized titles and meta descriptions</li><li>Use keyword placement</li><li>Optimize images and decrease load times</li><li>Incorporate responsive design into your website</li><li>Using Sitemaps properly</li><li>Making use of Robots.txt</li><li>Employ RSS feeds. To begin with SEO, you must first grasp what it is and how it works. Then, you can use the tips provided here to give your site the best chance of success in the competitive search engine landscape.</li></ol>



<h2>What&#8217;s the purpose of SEO?</h2>



<p>It is the practice of improving the ranking of a website on search engines. It is essential to get a higher rank on the search engine results page. Important for attracting users looking for your content and can lead to increased website traffic. How can I improve my website traffic?</p>



<p>Your site can get more traffic if you make résumés and social media profiles that show off your skills, and optimize your site for keywords.</p>



<h2>What are some different methods of Search Engine Optimization?</h2>



<p>There are many different methods of Search Engine Optimization you can use to improve your website traffic. The most common are keyword stuffing, adding metatags, and creating high-quality content. Each strategy has advantages and disadvantages, so choosing the right one for your website is essential.</p>



<h2>What happens if I don&#8217;t perform Search Engine Optimization?</h2>



<p>The search engines crawl the web continuously. When you make a website, you&#8217;re giving the search engines permission to read every page of your website. If you don&#8217;t optimize your site, you&#8217;re likely leaving valuable information on the table. Not optimizing your website can result in lost leads, missed opportunities, and an overall less successful online presence.</p>



<p>There aren&#8217;t any shortcuts to SEO success, but there are many ways to improve your odds.</p>



<h2>Methods of improving your website traffic with SEO</h2>



<p>Suppose you&#8217;re like most small business owners. In that case, your website is probably the first and most important place where potential customers find out about you. Unfortunately, few small businesses use search engine optimization (SEO) to improve their website traffic. And unfortunately, many don&#8217;t even realize that SEO is an option.</p>



<p>You can improve your website traffic with SEO in many ways. Still, the most common and effective methods include:</p>



<ul><li>Creating high-quality content that is keyword rich.</li><li>Use keywords in your site&#8217;s title tags and meta descriptions.</li><li>Placing links to your site throughout the web.</li></ul>



<p>You can also learn to create compelling blog content and promote it effectively through social media.</p>



<p>Once you&#8217;ve implemented a few basic SEO techniques, you&#8217;ll be on your way to increasing your website traffic dramatically. And if you haven&#8217;t already done so, now would be an excellent time to examine your website&#8217;s current traffic levels and see what needs to be done to increase them.</p>



<h2>How can you improve your website traffic using search engine optimization?</h2>



<p>SEO is the process of making your website visible to potential web users through optimized phrases or keywords that appear in the search engines. You can take many steps to optimize your website for better search engine visibility, including improving your website&#8217;s title, metadata (information about your website such as the name and description), social media promotion strategies, and link building. Additionally, implementing Google AdWords and other paid advertising strategies can help drive more traffic to your site from targeted searchers.</p>



<h2>Conclusion: what can be done after search engines have noticed you.</h2>



<p>There is no one-size-fits-all response to this topic, as the optimum technique to optimize differs depending on the situation. Your website for search engines will vary depending on the specific keywords and phrases being targeted and your website&#8217;s overall structure and layout. However, some general tips for optimizing your website for search engine visibility include adding high-quality content, making your website easy to visit, maximizing your search engine results, creating a website for mobile device viewing, and using external links to increase website traffic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/">What is SEO and why is it important?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">BigWing</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/what-is-seo-and-why-is-it-important/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
